# **Ronen Lapushner**

Cellphone: +972-50-2669606 Email: ronenk17@gmail.com Portfolio: ronen.xyz

I am a highly motivated full stack developer, with more than 5 years of vast, proven experience with many environments, looking for exciting opportunities to use my wide skill set to contribute and thrive. I'm currently enrolled in the Open University of Israel, studying for a Bachelors in CompSci.

#### **Professional Skills**

Languages/Platforms

- C99 / C++ (11+)
- Java (8+)
- Golang
- Python 3
- Rust
- Linux/Unix, Windows

#### Backend

- Cross-platform development with native tools
- Multithreding
- Multiprocessing
- POSIX / Win32
- Kubernetes (GCP)

#### **UI/Frontend Frameworks**

- C++ Qt5, wxWidgets, ImGui
- Java Swing
- Python
  PyQt, Tk
- JS vue.js

#### Software

- GCC Toolchain
- Valgrind
- LLVM Utilities
- Doxygen
- CMake, Autotools
- go\* tools, Cargo

## **Experience**

**Cyren** Software Engineer

September 2020 - Present September 2016 – January 2019

- Development and maintenance of a cross-platform, cross-architecture, full-stack application.
- Using LLVM's sanitizers to standardize and improve code quality.
- AGILE development and tight integration of customer relations.
- Rewriting old code with C++14-compliant code.
- Reverse engineering and Documentation of previously undocumented systems.
- Writing internal debugging utilities with Python 3.

### Israeli Air Force (IAF) – Ofek Unit Programmer

December 2013 - August 2016

- Honorable discharge with very high commendations.
- Development of highly-classified logistic and automation systems.
- Conceptualization, design and implementation of advanced communications and data systems.
- Full Stack End-to-End and prototyping using different development platforms.

# **Education / Certifications**

#### **Open University of Israel**

July 2018 - Present

• B.Sc. in Computer Science, 83 average.

**BASMACH** Shalishut Base, Ramat-Gan, Israel

September – December 2013

• NTMM (Nat-Mam) Course for DevOps engineers, graduated with excellence.

### Tchernichovski High School Netanya, Israel

September 2007 – June 2013

• Complete Matriculation diploma with 5 units in Computer Science and Physics.

## **Spoken Languages**

**Hebrew:** Native language **English:** Native level

Recommendations will be forwarded upon request.